Three hundred
ثلاثمائة
Three hundred and one
ثلاثمائة وواحد
Hanzi
هانز
I've been feeling really weak lately.
أشعر بضعف شديد في الآونة الأخيرة.
Working for Ms. Qin
العمل لدى السيدة تشين
must be exhausting, huh?
لا بد أن ذلك مرهق، أليس كذلك؟
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
A 24/7 corporate slave life.
حياة عبودية مؤسسية على مدار الساعة.
Anyone would be worn out.
أي شخص سيشعر بالإرهاق.
It's been three years.
لقد مرّت ثلاث سنوات.
Remember Vanka from the elementary school textbook?
هل تتذكرون فانكا من كتاب المدرسة الابتدائية؟
I've been a bonded laborer for three years.
لقد كنت عاملاً متعاقداً لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
Finally, I see a glimmer of hope.
وأخيراً، أرى بصيص أمل.
What goes around comes around.
ما يدور حولها ويأتي حولها.
Heaven spares no one.
السماء لا ترحم أحداً.
This is retribution.
هذا جزاء.
Retribution.
عقاب.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Um...
واحد...
Ms. Qin...
السيدة تشين...
Is she willing to let you go?
هل هي مستعدة للسماح لك بالرحيل؟
I don't know either.
لا أعرف أيضاً.
But the good thing is,
لكن الأمر الجيد هو،
she hasn't bothered me these past two days.
لم تزعجني خلال اليومين الماضيين.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
She actually hasn't summoned me for two whole days.
في الحقيقة، لم تستدعني منذ يومين كاملين.
So you really...
إذن أنت حقاً...
don't like me?
ألا تحبني؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
Hanzi!
يبتعد!
Lin Hai is back.
لين هاي عاد.
And...
و...
Talk tonight.
سنتحدث الليلة.
Come home for dinner.
تعال إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء.
Chairman Lin's orders.
أوامر الرئيس لين.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Hurry, hurry!
أسرعوا، أسرعوا!
This counts as burglary, doesn't it?
هذا يُعتبر سرقة، أليس كذلك؟
I must be crazy.
لا بد أنني مجنون.
Spending a weekend acting insane with you.
أقضي عطلة نهاية الأسبوع معك وأتصرف بجنون.
The locks for this house
أقفال هذا المنزل
were all bought by me personally.
اشتريتها جميعها بنفسي.
How can this be considered...
كيف يمكن اعتبار هذا...
Quick, quick, quick!
بسرعة، بسرعة، بسرعة!
Keep your voice down.
اخفض صوتك.
Stop.
قف.
Hurry.
عجل.
Looks like the code hasn't changed.
يبدو أن الكود لم يتغير.
Tofu!
توفو!
You go that way.
اذهب من ذلك الطريق.
I'll go this way.
سأسلك هذا الطريق.
Tofu!
توفو!
My little Tofu!
يا توفو الصغير!
Weren't my slam dunks just awesome?
ألم تكن ضرباتي الساحقة رائعة؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I heard your brother is back this time
سمعت أن أخاك قد عاد هذه المرة
to hold a painting exhibition.
لإقامة معرض للوحات الفنية.
I don't know about that.
لا أعرف شيئاً عن ذلك.
Don't tell me.
لا تخبرني.
I think...
أظن...
Actually, between you two brothers,
في الحقيقة، بينكما أيها الأخوان،
you could be a little...
قد تكون قليلاً...
What was that sound?
ما هذا الصوت؟
Grab it, grab it!
أمسك به، أمسك به!
Take it!
خذها!
Go, go, go!
إذهب! إذهب! إذهب!
You...
أنت...
You, you, you...
أنتَ، أنتَ، أنتَ...
What are you d-doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
How come after the divorce,
كيف حدث ذلك بعد الطلاق؟
you quit being a doctor
لقد تركت مهنة الطب
and switched to theft?
ثم تحول إلى السرقة؟
Theft?
سرقة؟
Are you insane?
هل أنت مجنون؟
I'm entering my own home.
أنا أدخل منزلي.
How is that theft?
كيف يُعتبر هذا سرقة؟
*Your* home?
منزلك؟
We agreed during the divorce,
اتفقنا أثناء إجراءات الطلاق،
this house is mine.
هذا المنزل ملكي.
How did it become *your* home?
كيف أصبح هذا المكان منزلك؟
Fine, the house is yours.
حسناً، المنزل لك.
Then Tofu is mine, right?
إذن، التوفو لي، أليس كذلك؟
Tofu is because you claimed him for yourself.
توفو هو لأنك ادعيت ملكيته لنفسك.
You didn't give me visitation rights.
لم تمنحني حقوق الزيارة.
I haven't even complained.
لم أشتكِ حتى.
You... you want visitation rights?
أنت... أنت تريد حقوق الزيارة؟
Are you worthy?
هل أنت جدير؟
How did you carry him for ten months and give birth?
كيف حملتِ به لمدة عشرة أشهر ثم أنجبتِه؟
How can you still be so mean?
كيف لا تزال بهذه القسوة؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
I'm not... what?
أنا لست... ماذا؟
Secretary Lin.
السكرتيرة لين.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
men, you're really disgusting.
يا رجال، أنتم مقرفون حقاً.
Just shut up.
اصمت.
If you're going to say that,
إذا كنت ستقول ذلك،
you, you, you...
أنتَ، أنتَ، أنتَ...
What?
ماذا؟
I'll say it.
سأقولها.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Let's talk inside.
لنتحدث في الداخل.
You shut up.
اصمت.
Hi, Secretary Lin.
مرحباً، سكرتيرة لين.
Get out.
اخرج.
Sorry about that.
أعتذر عن ذلك.
Secretary Lin.
السكرتيرة لين.
Bye, Secretary Lin.
مع السلامة، يا سكرتيرة لين.
They're arguing their way to the bed again.
إنهم يتجادلون في طريقهم إلى الفراش مرة أخرى.
Yeah.
نعم.
Same as always.
كما هو الحال دائماً.
Today is the weekend.
اليوم عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
Right.
يمين.
It is the weekend.
إنها عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
The weather is nice today.
الطقس جميل اليوم.
Boss.
رئيس.
Just forget it all.
انسَ كل شيء.
Forget about Secretary Lin too.
انسَ أمر السكرتيرة لين أيضاً.
Forget about today.
انسَ أمر اليوم.
Secretary Lin today...
وزيرة الخارجية لين اليوم...
forget about him too.
انسَ أمره أيضاً.
You can't forget, can you?
لا يمكنك أن تنسى، أليس كذلك؟
You can't forget Secretary Lin either, right?
ولا يمكنك نسيان السكرتيرة لين أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
Mom
أم
Your son is home.
ابنك في المنزل.
You must be tired. Come inside.
لا بد أنك متعب. تفضل بالدخول.
In my lifetime...
في حياتي...
...to see my eldest son again.
...لأرى ابني الأكبر مرة أخرى.
I'm truly blessed.
أنا محظوظ حقاً.
Dad.
أب.
Life as an artist treating you well?
هل تسير الحياة كفنان على ما يرام؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Before your work becomes immortal...
قبل أن يصبح عملك خالداً...
...you still remember your aging parents.
...ما زلت تتذكر والديك المسنين.
Such a filial son.
يا له من ابن بار!
The Virtuous Artist indeed.
الفنان الفاضل حقاً.
Great artist.
فنان عظيم.
Dad's still talking like that.
لا يزال أبي يتحدث بهذه الطريقة.
Yeah.
نعم.
Come on, son.
هيا يا بني.
Your dad's all bark and no bite.
والدك كثير الكلام قليل الفعل.
Don't mind his sarcasm.
لا تهتم بسخريته.
He actually knew you were coming back.
كان يعلم بالفعل أنك ستعودين.
He's been happy about it for a week.
لقد كان سعيداً بذلك لمدة أسبوع.
Hey, old man.
يا رجل عجوز.
If you want to see your son, come out.
إذا كنت تريد رؤية ابنك، فاخرج.
Stop eavesdropping.
توقف عن التجسس.
Mom.
أم.
Lin Han.
لين هان.
Still working as a secretary?
هل ما زلت تعملين كسكرتيرة؟
Still am.
ما زلت كذلك.
Back then, for that girl...
في ذلك الوقت، بالنسبة لتلك الفتاة...
...you ran away from home for independence.
...لقد هربت من المنزل بحثاً عن الاستقلال.
Then I heard you got dumped.
ثم سمعت أنك انفصلت عن حبيبك.
Your father found out.
لقد اكتشف والدك الأمر.
He told him to return to the Lin Family immediately.
أمره بالعودة إلى عائلة لين على الفور.
He said he'd come back later.
قال إنه سيعود لاحقاً.
I suppose it's my fault.
أظن أن هذا خطأي.
I raised the child...
لقد قمت بتربية الطفل...
...to be too responsible.
...أن يكون المرء مسؤولاً أكثر من اللازم.
Mom.
أم.
Little brother has always been outstanding.
لطالما كان الأخ الأصغر متميزاً.
I think...
أظن...
...he must have his own plans.
...لا بد أن لديه خططه الخاصة.
A bit willful, perhaps...
ربما يكون عنيداً بعض الشيء...
...but he's a good kid.
...لكنه فتى جيد.
Very reliable.
موثوق للغاية.
Your father's and my greatest pride...
أعظم فخر لي ولوالدك...
...is having you two sons.
...أن يكون لديك ولدان.
Come home soon.
عد إلى المنزل قريباً.
Your older brother is already back.
أخوك الأكبر قد عاد بالفعل.
It's a must.
إنه أمر لا بد منه.
Don't even think of making excuses.
لا تفكر حتى في اختلاق الأعذار.
At the very least...
على الأقل...
...let your dad and me, in our lifetime...
...دع والدك وأنا، في حياتنا...
...see the whole family reunited.
...رؤية العائلة بأكملها مجتمعة من جديد.
I understand.
أفهم.
Looks like they won't...
يبدو أنهم لن يفعلوا ذلك...
...be done anytime soon.
...سيتم الانتهاء منه في أي وقت قريب.
I have something to attend to. I should go.
لديّ أمرٌ عليّ القيام به. يجب أن أذهب.
I was just about to leave too.
كنت على وشك المغادرة أيضاً.
Let me give you a ride. It's on my way.
دعني أوصلك. إنها في طريقي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What's wrong with this elevator?
ما المشكلة في هذا المصعد؟
Hello? The elevator is broken.
أهلاً؟ المصعد معطل.
We're trapped inside.
نحن محاصرون في الداخل.
Please come fix it.
أرجوكم تعالوا لإصلاحها.
Okay, copy that.
حسناً، فهمت.
Wait for our rescue.
انتظروا إنقاذنا.
Darn it. What a piece of junk.
يا إلهي! يا لها من قطعة خردة!
Are you okay, Secretary Lin?
هل أنتِ بخير يا سكرتيرة لين؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Secretary Lin?
سكرتيرة لين؟
Secretary Lin!
سكرتيرة لين!
What's the matter with you?
ما بك؟
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
I'm not going.
لن أذهب.
I'm right here.
أنا هنا.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's fine. It's fine.
لا بأس. لا بأس.